question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
     "question": "The United States of America declared their independence from the British Empire on July 4th, 1776.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "The freshwater amphibian, the Axolotl, can regrow it&#039;s limbs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Art",
     "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
     "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
